Jo Wu

+61 468 843 853 | j0815wu@gmail.com | jowu.vercel.app

SUMMARY

A penultimate student of Science and Computer Science with a keen interest in security, code and maths. Strong creative and problem solving skills with a wide a lot of passion and variety of experiences in frontend development and project management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

University of New South Wales

Jan 2024 - Present

(Casual Academic) COMP6080: Frontend Programming Tutor

- Delivered lecture content on frontend practices and delegated exercises in tutorials, marking and administration, ensuring a positive experience for students.
- Mentored 30 students each week in creating interactive and modern web applications using CSS, HTML, JavaScript and ReactJS.

OpenWisdom Education Jul 2022 - Present

Web Developer

- Collaborated and communicated closely with project designer and marketing manager in planning and executing various projects, ensuring adherence to project timelines and products.
- · Delivered various web projects efficiently and consistently meeting or exceeding business quality standards

Freelance

Web Developer Jun 2021 - Jul 2022

• Organised and self-managed projects, while maintaining strong communication between clients, ensuring customer satisfaction and timeline adherence of deliverables.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Pokedex Jan 2023 - July 2024

Sole Programmer | github.com/jowhule/pokedex

- Designed a modern and minimalistic web application to cleanly display information to users, prioritising UI/UX.
- Utilised PokeAPI in conjunction with ReactTS and the MUI framework to implement content seamlessly on the webpage.

Personal Websites Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

Sole Programmer | <u>github.com/jowhule/jowu_portfolio</u> | <u>github.com/jowhule/my-page</u>

• Self-study of website practices and animations in CSS, HTML and JavaScript.

Keylogger Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

Sole Programmer | github.com/jowhule/keylogger

- Implemented a logger which sends keyboard and clipboard inputs to a dedicated email with Python.
- Self-studied in-place computer security measures and furthered understanding of modern security practices.

EDUCATION & EXTRACIRRICULAR ACTIVITIES

University of New South Wales

2021 - Present

Bachelors of Science / Computer Science, Statistics and Security Engineering

- People's Choice Arc Club Promotional Material Award (2023)
- Certificate of the Best Project Award in Computer Graphics (2024) awarded by Dr Ali Darejah

CSESoc (Computer Science and Engineering Society, UNSW)

Creative Subcomittee Member (2022 - 2023)

 Collaborated with directors and other members to produce and manage cross-platform content; merchandise, banners, reaching over 9,500 students each year. **DEVSoc** (Development Society, UNSW)

Trainee Member (2022 - 2022)

 Collaborated with a variety of peers to implement the backend and frontend for a restaurant calendar application.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Stacks / Languages

- Proficient: Python / JavaScript / TypeScript / React / C++ / PostgreSQL / HTML, CSS / Shell / Firebase / Latex / Git.
- Learning: Next.JS / C / Java / R / Adobe Suite.

Interests / Hobbies

 Digital illustration, learning Japanese, DIYs, crocheting, basketball